Guide to GMU Public Relations Press Releases
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
- GMU Public Relations- Press Releases
  - SHAKESPEARE'S TWELFTH NIGHT N.R. CUTLINE - MICHELLE LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS ELECTS OFFICERS. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU STUDENT AWARDED NVAA /NR CL/ SCHOLARSHIP, F. MOSHOS, A. ALLMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU STUDENT AWARDED EDISON NR, SCHOLARSHIP, F. MOSHOS, A, ALLMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - THE BRITISH ARE BACK M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - STUDENT NUMBERS AND QUALITY INCREASE AT GMU. - H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - INTERNATIONAL ASTROPHYSICS N.R, C.I. CONF: THE CRAB NEBULA, C. HILL. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU STAFF MEMBER RECEIVES NR, CUTLINE SCHOLARSHIP, A. ALLMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - 52 PICK-UP DEBATES IN GMU'S HARRIS THEATRE M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - CRAB NEBULA LECTURE MEDIA ADV. CANDACE HILL. (Box Box 22)
  - UPCOMING EVENTS AT GMU /C.I./ M/ LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU RECEIVES $5000. DONATION MOBIL OIL/ FRAN MOSHOS / N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - MELPAR, GM TEAM TO RETRAIN TEACHERS IN SCIENCE / JOAN ZIEMBA /N.R/ (Box Box 22)
  - ENVIRONMENTAL SCIENTIST JOINS GMU/ HELEN ACKERMAN /N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - MELPAR, GM TEAM TO RETRAIN TEACHERS IN PHYSICS /N.R. / J. ZIEMBA. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU STUDENTS RECEIVE $5000 FELLOWSHIP FROM WEST- GATE /N.R./ F. MOSHOS. (Box Box 22)
  - VA. GOVERNOR CHARLES ROBB APPOINTS FIVE MEMBERS TO GMU BOARD OF VISITORS. (Box Box 22)
  - AREA BLACK STUDENTS PARTICIPATES IN GMU'S SUMMER TRANSITION PROGRAM. (Box Box 22)
  - VIETNAMESE ARTIST VO DINH TO EXHBIT AT GMU'S METRO CAMPUS /N.R/ FRAN M. (Box Box 22)
  - THREE GMU LAW STUDENTS RECEIVE SCHOLARSHIPS/ FRAN MOSHOS / N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU OFFERS FITNESS PROGRAM, " REJUVENATE THE JOINTS" /M. LESANE/N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - GEORGE MASON OFFERS NURSING REFRESHING COURSE/M. LESANE /N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU SELECTED AS FOCAL INSTITUTE FOR THE FIRST NORTHERN VA. CO- (Box Box 22)
  - AUDITIONS - GMU THREE MUSICAL GROUPS. (Box Box 22)
  - PEDIATRIC NURSING COURSE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU PROFESSOR TO PARTICIPATE IN 1984 OLYMPIC SCIENTIFIC CONGRESS/ N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - STUDYING THE CREEK WAY OF LIFE N.R/ MICHELLE LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - FORMER FITCHBURG RESIDENT MAKES DEAN'S LIST AT GMU /N.R./FRAN MOSHOS. (Box Box 22)
  - REGISTRATION UNDERWAY FOR FINAL TERM OF GMU'S SUMMER SCHOOL/N.R./LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - PATRIOT CIRCLE CLOSES ! POWER OUT FRAN MOSHOS /FLASH. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU AWARDS ITS FIRST PRESIDENTIAL SCHOLARSHIP /N.R./ FRAN MOSHOS. (Box Box 22)
  - PROBLEMS FOR RACIAL AND ETHNIC RELATIONS.../M.A. / JOAN ZIEMBA. (Box Box 22)
  - NORTHERN VIRGINIA ORAL HISTORY COLLECTION OPEN AT GMU / JOAN ZIEMBA / N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - VEPCO AT IT AGAIN!/FLASH HELEN ACKERMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - GRADUATE DEGREES IN SYSTEM ENGINEERING AT TYSON & METRO /N.R. / C.I. / P.S.A. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU HOLDS DANCE AUDITIONS /C.I./ MICHELLE LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU FOUNDATION RECEIVES BROYHILL'S LEGISLATIVE PAPERS /N.R./ FRAN MOSHOS. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU HOLDS AUDITIONS FOR CHAMBER ORCHESTRA /P.S.A AND C.I./ M.LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - KIMBLE RECEIVES GRADUATE AWARD FOR CREATIVE WRITING /N.R. / J. ZIEMBA. (Box Box 22)
  - THE NEW CONFLICT MANAGERS N.R. / MICHELLE LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU ART PROFESSOR RECEIVES Guggenheim AWARD /N.R./ M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR OF UNIVERSITY RELATIONS APPOINTED AT GMU /N.R./ ACKER. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU MUSIC FACULTY FEATURED IN SONG RECITAL /M. LESANE /C.I./ AND P.S.A. (Box Box 22)
  - EIGHTY KOREAN STUDENTS TO VISIT GEORGE MASON UNIVERSITY THIS SUMMER. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU ENGLISH LANGUAGE INSTITUTE BEGINS SUMMER SESSION /N.R. / F. MOSHOS. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU ENGLISH INSTITUTE FRAN MOSHOS. CALENDER ITEM. (Box Box 22)
  - SCHOLARSHIP FUND FROM NAIOP N.R. / FRAN MOSHOS. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU ENLISTS AID OF FAIRFAX COMMUNITY IN SOLVING HOUSING CRUNCH / N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - "THE FEEDS" COME TO GMU /N.R. MICHELLE LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - CAREER COUNSELING CLOSED FOR SUMMER. (Box Box 22)
  - NEW ALUMNI DIRECTOR NAMED AT GEORGE MASON /N.R. / HELEN ACKERMAN - G. YODER. (Box Box 22)
  - WJLA NEWS REPORTER GRADUATES FROM BMU WITH A MASTER'S IN CLINICAL. (Box Box 22)
  - ELIZABETH DREW TO SPEAK AT GMU FOR MAY 10 GRADUATION /FRAN M./N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - THREE NEW DOCTORAL DEGREES AWARDED BY GMU / FRAN MOSHOS /N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - REGISTRATION UNDERWAY FOR TERM "A" OF GMU'S SUMMER SESSION /N.R./M.L. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU STUDENTS FIND SUMMER RIGHT TIME FOR UNUSUAL PROGRAM /N.R. / SS & ML. (Box Box 22)
  - HIGH TECH CADRE BUILDS AT GMU HELEN ACKERMAN /N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU TO HOST INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON INTERN'L ONFLICT MANAGEMENT. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU EXHIBIT STUDENT ART MICHELLE LESANE /N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - FIRST ROBINSON FELLOWSHIP AWARDED AT GMU / HELEN ACKERMAN / N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU FORENSICS TEAM ENDS SEASON IN THE TOP TEN/ N.R. /MICHELLE LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU TO HOST INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON INTERCULTURAL CONFLICT. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU'S INTERNATIONAL NURSING PROGRAM GETS ON THE MAP /N.R. / M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - SUMMER SAVINGS AT PATRIOT CLUB OUTDOOR MARKETS / ALAN SREBNICK /N.R, P.S.A. (Box Box 22)
  - TERMS "B" AND "C" GET UNDER WAY AT GMU / N.R. MICHELLE LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - PANEL ON U.N. CONVENTION ON CONTRACTS FOR THE INTERN'L SALE OF GOODS. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU DEBATES SUCCESSFUL AT NATION AT TOURNAMENT /N.R. / S. STOCKER AND M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - MEMORY AND OLDER ADULT DISCUSSED AT GMU / N.R. / S. STOCKER, M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU WINS EAST COAST CHAMPIONSHIP N.R. / S.STOCKER AND M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - ANNUAL REPORT 1984. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU JAZZ ENSEMBLE PERFORMS SPRING CONCERT /N.R. / M, LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - STATE NURSING BOARD REVIEW COURSE OFFERED AT GMU / N.R. /M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU FIRST VIRGINIA UNIVERSITY TO REQUIRE GRADUATE TRAINING FOR SECONDARY TEACHERS /N.R./ M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - SCHOOL UNIVERSITY PARTNERSHIP LUNCHEON. (Box Box 22)
  - $5 RISE IN PARKING FEES, DESIGNATION OF LOTS CHANGED / N.R. / H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU OFFERS FITNESS WORKSHOP FOR HEALTH PROFESSIONALS /N.R. /SS AND M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU OFFERS FITNESS PROGRAM, "REJUVENATE THE JOINS" /N.R. SS AND M.L. (Box Box 22)
  - MEMBER OF VA'S 51ST HOUSE OF DELEGATE TO GRADUATE /N.R. / FRAN MOSHOS. (Box Box 22)
  - RUNNER TAKES OFF WITH A DEGREE FROM GMU /N.R. / FRAN MOSHOS. (Box Box 22)
  - UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA PROFESSOR TO CONCLUDE GMU SERIES /N.R. - P.S.A /ML AND HA. (Box Box 22)
  - SUMMER SESSION ENROLLMENT /M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - LITERARY READINGS /N.R. / J. ZIEMBA. (Box Box 22)
  - POET WEIGL READS AT GEORGE MASON / N.R. / JOAN ZIEMBA. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU THEATER COMPANY PRESENTS THE FIRE RAISERS /N.R. / M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU PRESENTS 1984 FOREIGN FILM FESTIVAL /M.R. / M. LESANE (Box Box 22)
  - OVER 2000 EXHIBITS ON DISPLAY FOR NATIONAL HISTORY COMPETITION /N.R. / J.Z. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU FACULTY AND CHORALE PERFORM AT THE KENNEDY CENTER /N.R, P.S.A. / SS AND ML. (Box Box 22)
  - GERALD L. BALILES, ATTORNEY GEN. KEYNOTE'S GMU'S ANNUAL ALUMNI BANQUET. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU NORTHERN VIRGINIA SYMPHONIC CHORUS PRESENTS ENGLISH ANTHEMS /C.A. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU CHAMBER ORCHESTRA PRESENTS SPRING CONCERT / P.S.A. C.I. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU SYMPHONIC WIND PRESENT SPRING CONCERT /S.S. AND M.L / P.S.A. C.I. (Box Box 22)
  - FEDERAL TRADE COMMISSIONS MILLER ON PUBLIC CHOICE /M.A. / HELENA. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU FEATURES R2D2 ROBOT ON FIRST ANNUAL COMMUNITY TOUR /N.R. /M.L. (Box Box 22)
  - BUCHANAN RECEIVES SEIDMAN DISTINGUISHED AWARD IN POLITICAL ECONOMY. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU CHORALE IN CONCERT /C.I. / MICHELLE LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU HOLDS COUNSELLING CONFERENCE N.R./ MICHELLE LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GEORGE MASON VICE PRESIDENT APPOINTED TO HIO UNIVERSITY /N.R. /ACKER. (Box Box 22)
  - POET BRUTUS TO SPEAK AT GMU. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU INTERNATIONAL WEEK TO (N.R.)FEATURED EXHIBITS, ENTERTAINMENT /H.A. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU BANQUET FOCUSES ON ALUMNI STUDENT ACHIEVEMENT /N.R. /H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU CENTER FOR HEALTH PROMOTION TO CONDUCT HEALTH LIFESTYLE STUDY /N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - BLACK HISTORY MONTH CODE: 1-52010 (1984). (Box Box 22)
  - GMU ALUMNI ASSOCIATION SEEKS NOMINATIONS / N.R. / HELEN ACKERMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - THE MEANING OF THE RIGHT TO LIFE - THIRD LECTURE / N.R. / S. STOCKER, H.A. (Box Box 22)
  - SPRING CRAFTS FESTIVAL TO BE HELD AT GMU / SUSAN STOCKER S. H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - MEDIA ADVISORY NOTICE /H. ACKERMAN THE GENERATION, TRANSFER AND UNTIL TECH. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU PROJECT FOR THE STUDY OF YOUNG CHILDREN.../M. LESANE /N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU DANCE COMPANY PRESENTS ANNUAL SPRING CONCERT /S. STOCKER, M. LES. / CIPSA. (Box Box 22)
  - HEALY TO SPEAK AT GMU FOR UNIVERSITY DAY CELEBRATION / N.R. / M.L. (Box Box 22)
  - MAJOR BEQUEST TO BRING OUT - STANDING FACULTY TO GMU N.R. / H. ACKER. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU FORENSICS TEAM BEGANS SPRING SEASON WITH SUCCESS /N.R. / M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - LECTURE SERIES EXPLORES NATURAL LAWS AND NATURAL RIGHTS /N.R. H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU OFFERS WORKSHOP FOR NURSES ON ARTHRITIS MANAGEMENT / C.I./ M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU DIVISION OF NURSING CONTINUNING EDUCATION OFFER CLASSES /C.I. / M.LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - THE ART AND SKILL OF RESOLVING CONFLICT / N.R. / M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - HIGH TECH WORKSHOP ON MANAGEMENT FOR GROWTH /C.I. / H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU DEPT. OF PHYSICAL EDUCATION OFFERS FITNESS PROGRAM /N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - HIGHT - TECH JOB FAIR C.I. P.S.A. (Box Box 22)
  - NORTHWEST PROF. TO SPEAK N.R. - P.S.A. (Box Box 22)
  - CAPITAL CENTER TO HELP GEORGE MASON PLAN ARENA / N.R. / H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - CHOREOGRAPHER MOLISSA FENLEY TO PERFORM AT GMU /N.R., C.I. / P.S.A. / M.L. (Box Box 22)
  - CAMINA BURANA AT GEORGE MASON UNIVERSITY /C.I. /MICHELLE LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GOSPEL AT GEORGE MASON UNIVERSITY, C.I. / P.S.A. MICHELLE LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU LAUNCHES FUNDRAISING CAMPAIGN FOR MATHY HOURS /N.R. /P.J. (Box Box 22)
  - ADMISSIONS OFFERS NEW STUDENT SERVICE/ N.R. / P.J. AND S.S. (Box Box 22)
  - MARION MOHR IS 1983 RECIPIENT OF FOSTER B. GRESHAM AWARD /N.R. /P.J. (Box Box 22)
  - SENATOR WARNER TO SPEAK AT SEMINAR ON EMPLOYMENT OF THE DISABLED. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU EXHIBITS SCULPTURE IN FENWICK GALLERY / PENNY GOODMAN. /C.I. (Box Box 22)
  - CONTEMPORARY CALLIGRAPHY AND N.R. PAINTING FROM THE REPUBLIC OF CHINA /P.S.A. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU APPOINTS NEW DEVELOPMENT DIRECTOR / P. GOOSMAN / N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU OFFERS NURSING REFRESHER COURSE / M. LESANE / CALENDER ITEM. (Box Box 22)
  - LOCAL RESIDENTS PLACED ON GMU DEAN'S LIST / PENNY GOODMAN /N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - WATER OFF ! / FLASH / H.A. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU PRESENTS THE MONSTER, THE BRIDE AND STEPHAN /N.R / M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMI - TRW INDUSTRIAL AFFILIATE PROGRAM. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU ALUMNI ASSOCIATION SEEKS NOMINATIONS / N.R. / H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - PRINCETON PROFESSOR SPEAKS NATURAL LAW AND NATURAL RIGHTS /N.R. / H.A. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU EXHIBITS ROMANIAN PHOTOGRAPHY. (Box Box 23)
  - ARTHUR PETERSON IN ROBERT FROST: FIRE AND ICE. (Box Box 23)
  - FLESIHMAN [FLEISHMAN] TO SPEAK AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - VIRGINIANS GIVE STATE SCHOOLS HIGH MARKS. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU AWARDS ARENA CONTRACT. (Box Box 23)
  - GLORIANA SINGERS TO PERFORM. (Box Box 23)
  - VITA PROGRAM AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - REGISTRATION AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU DEAN RESIGNS. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU HOLDS WORKSHOP ON AGING. (Box Box 23)
  - FORMER CONGRESSWOMEN SHIRLEY CHISHOLM TO SPEAK AT GMU FOR BLACK HISTORY MONTH. (Box Box 23)
  - GOSPEL RECORDING STAR MYRNA SUMMERS TO PERFORM AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU HOLDS FOREIGN POLICY DISCUSSIONS. (Box Box 23)
  - LOIS CUCULLU NAMED MARY ROBERTS RINEHART SCHOLARSHIP WINNER. (Box Box 23)
  - WRITER RATHRYN ABDUL - BAKI NAMED MARY ROBERTS RINEHART SCHOLARSHIP WINNER. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU SYMPHONIC WINDS PERFORMS AT FAIRFAX HIGH SCHOOL. (Box Box 23)
  - Guggenheim FELLOW READS AT MASON. (Box Box 23)
  - TRIO DELL' ARTE - 1985. (Box Box 23)
  - DANCE IMPROVISATION. (Box Box 23)
  - " LITTLE LADY AND THE GIANTS" AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - ART PROFESSOR DISCUSSES SCULPTURE. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU PLANS PHONATHON. (Box Box 23)
  - CHARLES MOTTON DANCE CONCERT. (Box Box 23)
  - "WHO'S WHO" FROM GEORGE MASON. (Box Box 23)
  - NOBEL / AUREATE SPEAKS AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - GUITARIST TANENBAUM PERFORMS AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU PRESENTS LECTURE ON FEDERALISM. (Box Box 27)
  - GMU PRESENTS CONFERENCE ON BLACK WOMEN. (Box Box 23)
  - VIRGINIANS SUPPORT HIGHER EDUCATION. (Box Box 23)
  - SOCIETY AND ARTS LECTURE. (Box Box 23)
  - MOZART AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - WRITER IN RESIDENCE SERIES. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU CHORALE TO PERFORM IN CONCERT. (Box Box 23)
  - PIANIST YIN CHENG - ZONG AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - PIANIST MC DERMOTT AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU'S NEW TUITION PAYMENT PLAN. (Box Box 23)
  - OVERSEAS STUDY PROGRAMS. (Box Box 23)
  - CHAIM POTOK TO SPEAK AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - TECHNOLOGY AND CONSCIOUSNESS LECTURES. (Box Box 23)
  - LECTURE ON CHILD ABUSE, INCEST, RAPE PREVENTION. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU TO HOST EDUCATION AND CAREERS REVIEW PROGRAM. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU HOLDS AUDITIONS FOR MUSIC SCHOLARSHIPS. (Box Box 23)
  - HIGH TECH JOB FAIR. (Box Box 23)
  - ALUMNI REUNION BANQUET. (Box Box 23)
  - GERMAINE BREE VISITS GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - INTERNATIONAL WEEK 1985. (Box Box 23)
  - LOCAL AREA NETWORK (LAN) CONFERENCE. (Box Box 23)
  - DISTINGUISHED FACULTY AWARDS. (Box Box 23)
  - PEDIATRIC NURSING. (Box Box 23)
  - SIR ALAN WALTERS SPEAKS AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - STUDENT ART EXHIBITION AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - THE SHAPE OF THE FUTURE. (Box Box 23)
  - HYDRILLA IN THE POTOMAC. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU RECEIVES CHALLENGES GRANT OF $ 15. (Box Box 23)
  - WRITER MARCOS AGUINIS AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - TELEVISION DOCUMENTARIES / JOE / FOREMAN. (Box Box 23)
  - SUMMER SESSION. (Box Box 23)
  - HERITAGE GUILT ON DISPLAY. (Box Box 23)
  - NOMINEES SOUGHT FOR GMU BOARD OF VISITORS. (Box Box 23)
  - NEW SCHOOL OF INFORMATIONAL TECHNOLOGY. (Box Box 23)
  - TRANSFER GRANTS FOR MINORITY STUDENTS. (Box Box 23)
  - HEALTH FAIR AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - BASQUE STONE CARVER BEGINS. (Box Box 23)
  - CONDOS PROVIDE HOUSING FOR GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - TUITION AND FEES INCREASE. (Box Box 23)
  - AREA CORPORATION SURVEY. (Box Box 23)
  - PROFESSOR ALPHONSE CHADANIS AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - JOHN MC LAUGHLIN TO SPEAK AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - CRIMES OF THE HEART. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU SYMPHONIC WINDS. (Box Box 23)
  - SMALL BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU COMPUTER FAIR. (Box Box 23)
  - 100 BEST ECONOMISTS. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU DEBATE TEAM. (Box Box 23)
  - OPTIMIZING ADULT DEVELOPMENT. (Box Box 23)
  - FREE OUTDOOR DANCE CONCERT. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU CONTINUING EDUCATION HOLDS STATE BOARD. (Box Box 23)
  - FERMANDEZ - MORAN SPEAKS AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - HIGH TECH ENGINEERS JOIN GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU FORENSICS TEAM WINS. (Box Box 23)
  - GLORIANA SINGERS PERFORM AT KENNEDY CENTER. (Box Box 23)
  - GEOLOGY DEPT. HOLDS "DIAMOND" SEMINAR. (Box Box 23)
  - GABRIEL APPOINTED TO HEAD PERFORMING ARTS. (Box Box 23)
  - MANAGEMENT EXECUTIVE JOINS GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - JAZZ ENSEMBLE TO PERFORM. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU OFFER'S "TALL SHIPS" COURSE. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU EXPANDS COURSES IN ARLINGTON. (Box Box 23)
  - NATION'S FIRST PHD IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY. (Box Box 23)
  - OPEN HOUSE AT SMALL BUSINESS CENTER. (Box Box 23)
  - COMMENCEMENT 1985. (Box Box 23)
  - ROBINSON PROFESSORS. (Box Box 23)
  - LESANE APPOINTED ASST. DIRECTOR P.R. (Box Box 23)
  - NEW SCHOOL OF NURSING ANNOUNCED. (Box Box 23)
  - SUMMER INSTITUTE FOR MATH TEACHERS. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU AWARDS FIRST DOCTORAL IN PSYCHOLOGY. (Box Box 23)
  - DISABLED STUDENT AT GMU NAMED. (Box Box 23)
  - OUTDOOR MARKET. (Box Box 23)
  - HEMLOCK OVERLOOK. (Box Box 23)
  - FISHER TO JOIN GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU FACULTY MEMBERS AWARDED FELLOWSHIPS. (Box Box 23)
  - GLOBAL ISSUE PROGRAM. (Box Box 23)
  - MARY ROBERTS RINEHART FUND AWARDS. (Box Box 23)
  - SMALL BUSINESS CENTER WORKSHOP. (Box Box 23)
  - DANCE AUDITIONS. (Box Box 23)
  - CHORUS ADDITIONS. (Box Box 23)
  - PATRIOT CLUB GOLF TOURNAMENT. (Box Box 23)
  - ENGLISH COURSES FOR NON - NATIVE SPEAKERS. (Box Box 23)
  - CENTRAL RECEIVING ON THE MOVE. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU GRADUATE RECEIVES DEMPSEY AWARD. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU FORENSICS TEAM FINISHES NO.2 IN NATION. (Box Box 23)
  - PARKING LOTS TO CLOSE FOR REPAIRS. (Box Box 23)
  - GMU PRESENTS SUMMER ARTS EXPERIENCE. (Box Box 23)
  - INFORMATION SEMINAR - GRADUATE PROGRAM FOR BLACKS. (Box Box 23)
  - AUTHOR MOFFETT TO SPEAK AT GMU. (Box Box 23)
  - PULLING STRINGS AT NATIONAL MUSEUM (FTP). (Box Box 23)
  - FIRE ALARMS TO BE TESTED FLASH H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - TRAFFIC REROUTING FLASH H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - BQM ESTABLISHES $100,000 CHAIR AT GMU H.ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - NEW PROGRAM ON INFORMATIONAL RESOURCE MANAGEMENT H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU AND ROTARY SPONSOR STUDENT WORLD AFFAIRS CONF. H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - MARITIME VIEW OF ALEXANDRIA P.R H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - NEW ADMINISTRATIVE POSITION PR (V.P. MASH) H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - WEST RATE AWARDS $5,000 TO GMU PR. STUDENT H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU STUDENT ASSESS MIDEAST PR CONFLICT C. HILL. (Box Box 24)
  - INSTITUTE ON HUMANE STUDIES PR RELOCATES AT GMU C. HILL. (Box Box 24)
  - "DREAMSCAPE" MUSICAL FESTIVAL ( GLENN SMITH) C. HILL. (Box Box 24)
  - PARKING LOT K PATH CLOSED FLASH M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU DEAN ELECTED FELLOW OF AAAS PR (TOMBES) H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU CLASSES ON CABLE T.V. M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU PRESENTS SUMMER CONCERT C.I. P.S.A M.LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU STUDENT SELECTED AS GOVERNOR P.R. H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - SMALL BUSINESS WORKSHOP AT GMU P.R. P.S.A H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - WATER OFF IN ROBINSON II FLASH H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - GOV. ROBB APPOINTS GMU PROFESSOR TO BICENTENNIAL (COMMISSION G. PACHECO) M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU HOLDS PEDIATRIC REVIEW COURSE C.I. M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU SPONSOR REVIEW COURSE FOR ADULT NURSE PRACTITIONER C.I. M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU LURES SCIENTISTS BACK TO CLASSROOM P.R. (Box Box 24)
  - FIRE ALARM TO BE TESTED FLASH. H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - POWER OUT !! FLASH H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - SUMMERS AND PATRIOT MARKET P.R. P.S.A C.I. A. ALLMAN / H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - SYMPHONIC AUDITIONS C.I. P.S.A M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - WALCOTT TO READ AT GMU P.R. C.I. D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU SPONSORS FEDERAL THEATRE PROJECT ROSTER SHOW P.R. C.I. D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU HOSTS SMALL BUSINESS WORKSHOP C.I. P.S.A. H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU TO HOST COMMONWEALTH PROFESSORS D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - CENTER FOR SUPERCOMPUTER APPLICATIONS AT GMU M.A. P.R. (Box Box 24)
  - DANCER BLONDELL CUMMINGE AT GMU P.R., C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 24)
  - METROPOLITAN AREA ASSESSMENT CENTER M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU SITE FOR "GREENHOUSE EFFECT" TELECONFERENCE P.R. A. ALLMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - CLAUDIA MURPHY DANCE CO. TO PERFORM AT GMU P.S.A. D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - "COME LOVE WITH ME" AT GMU P.A. P.S.A. (Box Box 24)
  - UPCOMING CULTURE EVENTS AT GMU C.I. D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU PROFESSOR FENWICK FELLOW P.R. (BROCK BROWN) D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU TO OFFER CLINICAL TECHNOLOGY UPDATE TO RN'S P.R. D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU TO OFFER "HEALTH ASSESSMENT COURSE TO RN'S P.R. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU TO PRESENT STRATEGIC DEFENCE LECTURE SERIES D. BROWN C.I. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU SIGNS CAPITAL CENTER TO MANAGE PATRIOT CENTER P.R. H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - THE PAYROLL OFFICE HAS MOVED FLASH M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - NUMBER, SAT'S UP AT GMU P.R. H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - PIECES OF A DREAM COME TO GMU P.R. P.S.A. C.L. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU TO RESENT SCAPINO! P.R. P.S.A. D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU DEBATE TEAM P.R. M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - ANTHROPOLOGIST HARRIS AT GMU C.I. P.S.A. H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - SMALL BUSINESS FINANCING WORKSHOP C.I. H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - OCTOBER CALENDER OF EVENTS C.I. D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - SPYRO GYRA AT GMU. P.R. P.S.A. C.L. M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - SEXUAL STEREOTYPING TO CONTINUE (KENNETH ROACH) D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - NOBEL WEINER TO VISIT GMU (BETTY WILLIAMS PERPINS D. BROWN P.R. (Box Box 24)
  - "PLAYWRIGHT SHOWCASE" LAUNCHED AT GMU D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - TRANSPORTATION WORKSHOP AT GMU FOCUSES ON FUNDING SOURCES P.R. M.A. H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU LAUNCHES 1985 INTERNATIONAL FILM FESTIVAL C.I. D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - LONE JUSTICE COMES TO GMU. P.R. C.L. M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU A SERIES OF FREE P.R. CLASSICAL CONCERTS P.R. M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - GEAN CARRINGTON COOK CONCERT AT GMU D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - NO. VA. SYMPHONY AT GMU WITH JAZZ ENSEMBLE P.R. D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - ASTRONOMY LECTURE ON JUPITER AT GMU C.I. (Box Box 24)
  - KISS OF SPIDER WOMEN NOVELIST AT GMU ( MANUEL PUIG) D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - A CAR FOR THE ARTS P.R. C.L. H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU PRESENTS LECTURE ON APARTHEID LEADER MANDELA P.A. M.A. D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - MEDIA COVERAGE OF MIDDLE EAST DISCUSSED AT GMU P.R. D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - INTERNATIONAL ARTS FESTIVAL 1985- 86 M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - DR. SOBIN TO SPEAK ON "AIDS" P.R. M.A. P.S.A. D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU CAMPUSES HOST ART SHOWS P.R. D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU ANNOUNCES NEW ADMISSION PLAN (5827 PLAN) P.R. M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - COMPUTER WORKSHOP ON COMMERCIAL REAL ESTATE DEVELOPMENT APPRAISAL M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU WORKSHOP ON LOTUS FOR REAL ESTATE M. LESANE. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU PRESENTS "AS YOU LIKE IT" P.R. C.L. D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU HOLDS SHAKESPEAREAN WORKSHOP D. BROWN. (Box Box 24)
  - NOVELIST TONI MORRISON TO APPEAR AT GMU. (Box Box 24)
  - GMU NURSING PROGRAM HOLDS "WELLNESS IN CHRONIC ILLNESS" SEMINAR M. LESANE. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU SYMPHONY ORCHESTRA TO STAGE FIRST CONCERT P.R. D. BROWN. (Box Box 25)
  - COMPUTER EXPERT SPEAKS AT GMU C.I. (ROBERT GACOB) H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU HOLDS OPEN HOUSE C.I. P.S.A. P.R. M. LESANE. (Box Box 25)
  - DOING BUSINESS WITH GOVERNMENT WORKSHOP AT GMU. C.I. P.S.A. (Box Box 25)
  - GLENN SMITH NAMED COMPOSER - IN - RESIDENCE D. BROWN. P.R. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU LISTED IN " BEST BUYS IN COLLEGE EDUCATION D. BROWN. (Box Box 25)
  - EZRA POUND FILM FEATURED AT GMU P.R. C.I. C.L. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU DEBATE TEAM FEATURED ON PBS SERIES M. LESANE. (Box Box 25)
  - G. GORDON LIDDY TO LECTURE AT GMU C.I. P.S.A. D. BROWN. (Box Box 25)
  - FENICAL WATERCOLOR ON EXHIBIT AT METRO CAMPUS D. BROWN. (Box Box 25)
  - CHINESE COMPUTER DELEGATION AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 25)
  - PAYROLL DISTRIBUTION (THANKS GIVING) FLASH. (Box Box 25)
  - SHARE A HOLIDAY MEAL WITH GMU STUDENT C..I. P.S.A. (Box Box 25)
  - BURFORD MC CARTHY SPEAKS AT GMU P.R. C.I. D. BROWN. (Box Box 25)
  - PEACE EXPERT DISCUSS NATIONAL INTEREST. C.I. N.R. M.A. H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 25)
  - CHRISTMAS FUNFARE CONCERT AT GMU P.R. P.S.A. (Box Box 25)
  - FALL DANCE CONCERT WITH ARNICE ZANE AT GMU P.R. P.S.A. D. BROWN. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU PROFESSOR RELEASE NEW DATA ON COMPUTERPHOBIA M. LISANE. (Box Box 25)
  - GEFFREY COMES TO GMU C.L. M. LESANE. (Box Box 25)
  - JESSE L. JACKSON TO SPEAK AT ANNUAL WINTER CRAFT SHOW. FLASH (Box Box 25)
  - PAYROLL OFFICE WILL BE CLOSED FOR HOLIDAYS H.A. FLASH. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU TO OFFER SERIES OF CHRISTMAS MUSIC CONCERTS D. BROWN P.R. (Box Box 25)
  - BEETHOVEN BIRTHDAY CONCERT AT GMU P.R. C.I. D. BROWN. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU INDOCHINA INSTITUTE SPONSORS VIETNAMESE ARTIST. D. BROWN P.R. C.I. (Box Box 25)
  - GMU PRESENTS SECOND INTERNATIONAL ARTS FESTIVAL M. LESANE / R. CARROLL P.R. P.S.A. (Box Box 25)
  - HISTORIAN TO SPEAK AT GMU ON THE FRENCH REVOLUTION D. BROWN P.R. C.I. (Box Box 25)